we are excited to announce two new
programs at The Institute research
fellows for individuals working in the
field of active inference and
Partnerships for organizations looking
to engage with and support the active
inference ecosystem this video is going
to look at the websites for both
programs you can learn more at fellows
and partnerships. active inference do
Institute for research fellows we're
looking to catalyze the journeys and the
contributions of researchers in active
inference from all over the world
different career stages we will explore
and develop this introduction of the
program together and we'll continue to
update the website with different
questions that are
asked we're looking for an application
or a pre-submission inquiry describing
one or more research projects in detail
Andor outlining a more general direction
there's more details on the application
and the terms on that
site for Partnerships we are looking for
ways to develop synergistic
relationships with other organizations
that are in and adjacent to the active
inference ecosystem this could be across
different domains disciplines regions
languages backgrounds so it'll be really
awesome to explore what this looks like
we imagine that there'll be a lot of
variation among partner organizations in
the kinds of contributions and
affordances on both sides and so here
especially we're looking for uh
beginning a conversation while also
having the application template in mind
as we begin also figuring out terms that
make things work for different kinds of
Partners so we hope that these are some
interesting opportunities for you or to
share with someone that you know and we
look forward to how research fellows and
future other kinds of fellows and how
all different kinds of Partners can
start to do some really awesome things
in the ecosystem together all right
email blanket active inference Institute
with any questions or comments on this
bye